PUNEET VATSAYAN

Puneet is a serial entrepreneur, international business executive, and mentor. Puneet has lead many lives and has been an entrepreneur in both India and US; an angel investor in business enterprises in India, US and Europe. Puneet has worked in diverse industries with a global footprint.

Puneet is the Managing Director of PKV Advisors an advisory firm that works with entrepreneurs and management teams to significantly scale and transform their businesses. PKV Advisors has represented and facilitated the India entry of a number of large companies. Puneet is actively involved as a board member and advisor with a number of companies and VC / PE Funds. Puneet has been a past Trustee and Global Board Member of TiE Global. Puneet has also been on the CII National Committee on Information Technology.

As a serial entrepreneur he successfully founded, scaled and exited 3 ventures in India and Silicon Valley. In addition, he founded Hatch Incubators, which at one point was India's largest incubator. Prior to starting his entrepreneurial career in 2000 he worked with Centigram Communications / ADC Communication in worldwide product management, international marketing; and services marketing groups. In addition, he has worked with Measurex Corporation and U.S. Borax / RTZ in International marketing and business development.

Widely traveled, Puneet has spoken at a number of industry events, symposium and standard body meetings. He has been profiled in a number of magazines, newspapers and media articles.

EXPERIENCE:

Jan 2015 to	PKV Advisors
Present	Founder and Managing Director
	PKV Advisors is a boutique strategic advisory firm that works with entrepreneurs
	and management teams to significantly scale and transform their businesses. PKV
	Advisors has represented and facilitated the India entry of a number of large
	companies. PKV Advisors work very closely with PE firms on investment and
	operational mandates.
2010 to 2013	Co-Founder and Chairman
	Hatch Incubators
	As Co-Founder and Chairman of Hatch Incubators, set up India's largest multi-
	location incubator to identify and support "winning entrepreneurs".
2004 to 2010	Co-founder and Managing Director
	Mobera Systems Pvt. Ltd.
	As Co-founder and Managing Director of Mobera Systems, built a leading contract
	research and development outsourcing company with expertise in multiple
	sectors including communications, storage, defence, consumer internet, and
	security.
2001 to 2003	Co-Founder and CEO
	CNC Inc.
	CNC Inc, based in Silicon Valley was founded after the dot-com bust and was a roll
	up of services companies in the networking and communications industry.

1998 to 2000	Co-founder and CEO
	ViV-Echange Inc.
	ViV- Exchange Inc. based in Silicon Valley was an early SAAS and technology e-
	enablement platform for distributors in the US pharmaceutical and healthcare
	sector
1995 to 1998	Senior Product Manager – SMS, Unified Messaging
	Market Manager – Asia
	Centigram Communications
	Centigram Communication, based in Silicon Valley was an early telecom pioneer
	and market leader of SMS gateways, prepaid platforms, unified messaging, and
	enhanced services. Puneet held multiple responsibilities at Centigram
	Communications. As Market Manager for Asia he had complete marketing
	responsibility for the region and supported the sales and country offices in China,
	Korea, Taiwan, Hong Kong, Japan, Philippines, Singapore, Australia, and India. As
	Senior Product Manager, he worked very closely with key customers and the
	engineering team to define and deliver on the next generation of technology for
	SMS platforms and unified messaging.
1994 to 1995	International Marketing Manager
	Measurex (Honeywell)
	Measurex Corporation based in Silicon Valley was a pioneer in sensors and
	scanners used in continuous manufacturing industries globally. Puneet had global
	marketing responsibilities and supported the global sales teams in paper and steel
	industries.
1992 to 1994	Market Analyst
	U.S. Borax.
	U.S. Borax (Part of RTZ) was the global market leader in the mining of Borax and
	Borates. As Market Analyst, Puneet performed the role of global market and
	pricing analysis using advanced psychometric models.

OTHERS:

Global Board Member and Trustee – TiE Global President – TiE Punjab and Chandigarh

Nov 2009 to Dec 2012 Aug 2008 to Dec 2012

TiE is the world's largest organization that nurtures supports entrepreneurship globally. TiE headquartered in Silicon Valley has 12,000+ members in 60+ Chapters and 15 Countries including major cities like Silicon Valley, Los Angeles, New York, London, Frankfurt, Manchester, Singapore, Hong Kong, Mauritius, Mumbai and Delhi.

EDUCATION:

Masters in International Business

American Graduate School of International Management (Thunderbird), Glendale, USA

Bachelor in Engineering (Mechanical Engineering)